{
  "title": "New Question for G+12 and Unlimited - Part 1",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Tops of all piles shall be embedded at least in concrete pile cap.",
      "options": {
        "A": "150mm",
        "B": "100mm",
        "C": "125mm",
        "D": "75mm"
      },
      "answer": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "The distance between the center of gravity of compression and center of gravity of tension of the steel beams is called",
      "options": {
        "A": "Overall depth",
        "B": "Clear depth",
        "C": "Total depth",
        "D": "Effective depth"
      },
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "In plate girder bending moment is primarily resisted by",
      "options": {
        "A": "Web Plate",
        "B": "Flange angle",
        "C": "Flange plate",
        "D": "All"
      },
      "answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Horizontal stiffeners are used in girders to prevent web buckling due to",
      "options": {
        "A": "Bending",
        "B": "Shear",
        "C": "Point load",
        "D": "Diagonal cracks"
      },
      "answer": "B"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Vertical stiffeners are used in plate girders to prevent web buckling due to",
      "options": {
        "A": "Buckling",
        "B": "Load",
        "C": "Moment",
        "D": "Shear"
      },
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Bearing stiffeners are used to prevent deformation against large",
      "options": {
        "A": "Bending",
        "B": "Moment",
        "C": "Shear",
        "D": "Pointed loads"
      },
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "The maximum allowable lateral displacement of the shoring system is",
      "options": {
        "A": "20mm",
        "B": "30mm",
        "C": "L/180",
        "D": "40mm"
      },
      "answer": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "The maximum deflection of shoring if the road is away more than 5m is",
      "options": {
        "A": "30mm",
        "B": "25mm",
        "C": "50mm",
        "D": "40mm"
      },
      "answer": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "The maximum deflection of shoring system if the road is adjacent or less than 5m",
      "options": {
        "A": "25mm",
        "B": "20mm",
        "C": "40mm",
        "D": "30mm"
      },
      "answer": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "The minimum spacing of anchors in shoring system is",
      "options": {
        "A": "1m",
        "B": "3m",
        "C": "1.5m",
        "D": "1.2m"
      },
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Maximum grout length for anchors in shoring is",
      "options": {
        "A": "3m",
        "B": "5m",
        "C": "7m",
        "D": "10m"
      },
      "answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "The minimum depth of unplanned excavation for shoring system as per DM is",
      "options": {
        "A": "1m",
        "B": "2m",
        "C": "3m",
        "D": "0.5m"
      },
      "answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "If the soil type is less firm and need water to retain then piles are used in shoring.",
      "options": {
        "A": "Contiguous piles",
        "B": "Sheet piles",
        "C": "Secant piles",
        "D": "Any one"
      },
      "answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "The correct statement about secant piles and contiguous piles is that",
      "options": {
        "A": "All secant piles are having reinforcement",
        "B": "Contiguous piles are overlapped",
        "C": "Secant Piles are overlapped",
        "D": "None of above"
      },
      "answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "If all the piles of the building foundations are of 75cm diameter then static load test is required for what percent of the piles?",
      "options": {
        "A": "2%",
        "B": "3%",
        "C": "5%",
        "D": "1%"
      },
      "answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "Dynamic load test is required for what % of the piles in the foundation.",
      "options": {
        "A": "1%",
        "B": "2%",
        "C": "100%",
        "D": "5%"
      },
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Sonic test for piles is required for at least what %?",
      "options": {
        "A": "1%",
        "B": "2%",
        "C": "5%",
        "D": "10%"
      },
      "answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Integrity test is required for at least what % of all the piles?",
      "options": {
        "A": "10%",
        "B": "20%",
        "C": "50%",
        "D": "100%"
      },
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "The minimum steel bars required in pile design to achieve the ductility as per DM is",
      "options": {
        "A": "5%",
        "B": "3%",
        "C": "1%",
        "D": "0.5%"
      },
      "answer": "B"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "The minimum steel bars diameter for main steel and stirrups for piles are",
      "options": {
        "A": "10mm, 8mm",
        "B": "10mm, 10mm",
        "C": "16mm, 12mm",
        "D": "12mm, 10mm"
      },
      "answer": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "The minimum pile spacing as per DM rules is",
      "options": {
        "A": "1.5D",
        "B": "2D",
        "C": "3D",
        "D": "2.5D"
      },
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "The maximum out of position allowed for piles is",
      "options": {
        "A": "7mm",
        "B": "25mm",
        "C": "50mm",
        "D": "75mm"
      },
      "answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "The maximum limit for crack width due to tension load for tension piles is",
      "options": {
        "A": "0.1mm",
        "B": "0.5mm",
        "C": "0.3mm",
        "D": "0.2mm"
      },
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "Cross hole sonic logging test is usually done if the diameter and length of piles is",
      "options": {
        "A": "1m, 15m",
        "B": "1.5m, 20m",
        "C": "75cm, 20m",
        "D": "1m, 20m"
      },
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "Which of the following is not the grade of bolt used?",
      "options": {
        "A": "5.6",
        "B": "8.8",
        "C": "10.9",
        "D": "6.6"
      },
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "The overall lateral deflection for the building due to wind pressure shall not exceed",
      "options": {
        "A": "H/300",
        "B": "H/400",
        "C": "H/500",
        "D": "H/600"
      },
      "answer": "C"
    }
  ]
}
